Witness a true story of risking it all to fight for what you believe in.
Springsteen: Deliver Me from Nowhere is a drama,
music film directed by Scott Cooper.
Bruce Springsteen, a young musician on the cusp of global superstardom, struggles
to reconcile the pressures of success with the ghosts of his past.
Bruce Springsteen, played by Jeremy Allen White.
Jon Landau, played by Jeremy Strong.
Mike Batlan, played by Paul Walter Hauser.
Douglas Springsteen, played by Stephen Graham.
Faye Romano, played by Odessa Young.
Adele Springsteen, played by Gaby Hoffmann.
Springsteen: Deliver Me from Nowhere is a 2025 American biographical musical
drama film starring Jeremy Allen White as Bruce Springsteen.
Written and directed by Scott Cooper, and based on the 2023 book Deliver Me from Nowhere by Warren Zanes, as well as some elements from Springsteen's 2016
autobiography Born to Run,  it chronicles Springsteen's personal and professional struggles during the conception of his 1982 album Nebraska.
The film also stars Jeremy Strong, Paul Walter
Hauser, Stephen Graham, and Odessa Young.
Springsteen: Deliver Me from Nowhere had its world premiere at the 52nd Telluride Film Festival on August 29,
2025, and was theatrically released in United States by 20th Century Studios on October 24, 2025.
It received mixed reviews from critics, with White's and Strong's performances receiving praise,
but was criticized for repetitive plot points and tropes of musician biopics.
The film explores themes of depression, based on novel or book,
biography, mental health, singer-songwriter.
The tone is emotional.